Finding Aid for James K. Pollock Papers, 1920-1968
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Germany: Research and Official Responsibilities, 1935-1967, 16 linear feet
  - Office of the Military Government for Germany (U.S.) 1945-1946 and later official observatory and fact-finding missions to Germany, 1947, 1948, 1950
    - Länderrat
      - Secretary General Rossman's speeches 1946-1948 (Box 60)
        [60-18]
      - Speeches of Minister Presidents 1946-1948 (Box 60)
        [60-19]
      - Extracts from Monthly Reports of Military Government on Länderrat 1945-1946 (Box 60)
        [60-20]
      - Monthly Report for the Government Governor on Länderrat 1947-1948 (Box 60)
        [60-21]
      - Länderrat Committee materials 1946-1948
        - Mainly labor, social insurance, labor allocation, labor law and wages (Box 60)
          [60-22]
        - Housing, factory inspection, refugees, German Central Distribution, public health (Box 60)
          [60-23]
        - Education, POWs, emigration, public welfare, veterans (Box 60)
          [60-24]
        - Monthly Progress Reports (Box 60)
          [60-25]
      - Dissertation by Anton Pfeiffer: "Der Länderrat der Amerikanischen Zone" (University of Munich) 1948 (Box 60)
        [60-27]
    - Administrative (OMGUS)
      - Joint Conference of German Officials in the U.S.-British Zones 1946 (Box 60)
        [60-3]
      - Bizonal memoranda and policy statements 1946-1947 (Box 60)
        [60-4]
      - Food and Agricultural Administration 1946 (Box 60)
        [60-5]
      - Munich Conference of Minister Presidents May 1947 (Box 60)
        [60-9]
      - USFET/OMGUS Directives, Governmental Structure 1945-1946 (Box 60)
        [60-10]
      - James K. Pollock file on financial matters while working for OMGUS 1945-1948 (Box 60)
        [60-26]
    - Pollock Material 1945-1946
      - Refugees (Box 61)
        [61-1]
      - No. 1 Papers (memoranda, notes, observations)
        - October 1945-December 1945 (Box 61)
          [61-2]
        - January 1946-March 1946 (Box 61)
          [61-3]
        - April 1946-July 1946 (Box 61)
          [61-4]
      - Current Notes and Memoranda
        - November 1945-December 1945 (Box 61)
          [61-5]
        - January 1946-April 1946 (Box 61)
          [61-6]
        - May 1946-July 1946 (Box 61)
          [61-7]
      - Personal Letters, 3 folders (Box 61)
        [61-8; 61-9; 61-10]
    - Reports, etc
      - Proposed Constitutions for German States 1946-1947 (Box 61)
        [61-11]
      - OMG Hesse Chronology 1944-1947 (Box 61)
        [61-12]
      - Election materials 1946, 2 folders (Box 61)
        [61-13; 61-14]
      - President's Economic Mission to Germany (Hoover) 1947 (Box 61)
        [61-15]
      - OSS Research and Analysis Branch report: "Principal Post-Nazi German Officials" August 6, 1945 (Box 61)
        [61-16]
      - "Confidential Report to Senate Committee Investigating the National Defense Program, on the Preliminary Investigation of Military Government in the Occupied Areas of Europe," prepared by George Meader November 22, 1946 (Box 61)
        [61-17]
      - Orders concerning German education 1947 (Box 61)
        [61-18a]
      - Report to Secretary of War Patterson by Robert Moses on the German occupation July 12, 1947 (Box 61)
        [61-18b]
      - Report to the Council of Foreign Ministers from the Allied Central Authority in Germany
        - February 1947 (Secs. I, II) (Box 61)
          [61-19]
        - February 1947 (Sec. III) (Box 61)
          [61-20]
        - February 1947 (Sec. IV, Parts 1-4: Economic Problems) (Box 61)
          [61-21]
        - February 1947 (Sec. IV, Parts 5-8: Economic Problems) (Box 61)
          [61-22]
        - February 1947 (Sec. IV, Parts 9-11: Economic Problems) (Box 62)
          [62-1]
        - February 1947 (Secs. V-VI) (Box 62)
          [62-2]
        - February 1947 (Secs. VII-IX) (Box 62)
          [62-3]
      - "Summary of Principal Differences in Quadripartite Report for the Council of Foreign Ministers" March 1947 (Box 62)
        [62-4]
      - "Inter-Divisional Committee of German Governmental Structure" 1946 (Box 62)
        [62-5]
      - "The Evolution of Bizonal Organization" 1948 (Box 62)
        [62-6]
      - Bizonal matters 1947-1948 (Box 62)
        [62-7]
      - London Agreements 1948 (Box 62)
        [62-8]
      - Washington Agreement 1949 (Box 62)
        [62-9]
      - 1946 German elections (Box 62)
        [62-10]
    - Dated miscellanea
      - 1945 undated (Box 62)
        [62-11]
      - May 25, 1945-August 10, 1945 (Box 62)
        [62-12]
      - August 22, 1945-September 7, 1945 (Box 62)
        [62-13]
      - September 11, 1945-October 12, 1945 (Box 62)
        [62-14]
      - October 13, 1945-December 1946 (Box 62)
        [62-15]
      - 1947 (Box 62)
        [62-16]
      - January 6, 1948-April 28, 1948 (Box 62)
        [62-17]
      - April 29, 1948-June 18, 1948 (Box 62)
        [62-18]
    - Miscellanea
      - Bavaria, Württemberg-Baden, the Bremen Enclave, and the Soviet Union 1945-1948 (Box 62)
        [62-19]
      - Memoranda and reports on Hessen-Nassau July 1945-January 1946 (Box 62)
        [62-20]
      - Economic Council of the Bizonal Economic Area 1948 (Box 62)
        [62-21]
      - Correspondence June 26, 1945-October 1, 1945, May 18, 1948 (Box 62)
        [62-22]
      - Miscellanea (Box 62)
        [62-23]
      - Telephone directories and lists of occupation personnel 1945-1948 (Box 63)
        [63-1]
      - "My Notes on Germany" (Box 63)
        [63-2]
    - Collected Materials (largely published government documents)
      - Graphic material concerning organizational proposals for the Occupation Government 1945-1947 (Box 63)
        [63-3]
      - Graphic material giving economic, demographic and other data on occupation (Box 63)
        [63-4]
      - Graphic material, including maps of Occupied Germany (Box 63)
        [63-5]
      - Graphic material on the organization of the Federal Republic (Box 63)
        [63-6]
      - Special Report of the Military Governor, U.S. Zone
        - "Germany's Eastern Boundaries (Text and Graphics)" 1947 (Box 63)
          (incomplete)
          [63-7]
        - "Governmental Organization in Occupied Germany (Text and Graphics)" 1947 (Box 63)
          [63-8]
        - "Elections in Germany (Text and Graphics)" 1946-1947 (Box 63)
          [63-9]
      - Graphic material on the Structure of Land Ministries, U.S. Zone (Box 63)
        [63-10]
      - Graphic material on German Elections 1947, 1949 (Box 63)
        [63-11]
      - "Summary of CFM Agreements and Disagreements on Germany" 1947 (Box 63)
        (detailed breakdown of Four Power Positions at the Fourth Session of CFM, Moscow)
        [63-12]
      - "Summary of U.S. Statements and Proposals on German Government" Prepared by CFM Secretariat, CAD, OMGUS 1948 (Box 63)
        [63-13]
      - "Chronological Tables on Western Germany, 1947-1948" Prepared by CFM Secretariat, CAD, OMGUS May 15, 1949 (2 parts) (Box 63)
        [63-14; 63-15]
      - "Documented Chronology on Western Germany 1948" Prepared by CFM Secretariat, CAD, OMGUS January 15, 1949 (Box 63)
        [63-16]
      - "Bundesstaatliche Verfassungen" Prepared by CFM Secretariat, CAD, OMGUS 1948 (Box 63)
        (a comparison of federal constitutions)
        [63-17]
    - Clippings, Personal, and Later Material
      - Re occupation of Germany, especially concerns the Länderrat (Box 64)
        [64-1]
      - Occupation of Germany 1945-1946 (Box 64)
        [64-2]
      - Printed (largely OMGUS) 1945-1946 (Box 64)
        [64-3]
      - James K. Pollock farewell address to the Länderrat and Rossman's reply August 13, 1946 (Box 64)
        [64-5]
      - James K. Pollock speech on occupation prepared for U-M television 1965-1966 (Box 64)
        [64-6]
      - Miscellanea re Adenauer's 90th birthday, his death, and the 20th anniversary of the founding of the Länderrat 1965-1967 (Box 64)
        [64-7]
      - File (marked "I"/top) 1945-1949, 2 folders (Box 64)
        [64-8; 64-9]
      - Graphic material on U.S. Zone (Box 64)
        [64-10]
      - Re General Lucius Clay (largely clippings) (Box 64)
        [64-11]
      - German occupation general
        - 1947-1948 (Box 64)
          [64-13]
        - 1949-1951 (Box 64)
          [64-12]
      - Germany miscellanea 1950-1953 (Box 64)
        [64-14]
      - American occupation of Germany, 2 folders (Box 64)
        [64-15; 64-16]
  - University of Michigan Civil Affairs Training School
    - Course Materials 1943-1944, 5 folders (Box 64)
      [64-17; 64-18; 64-19; 64-20; 64-21]
    - Course Materials (military government problems) 1943-1944 (Box 64)
      [64-22]
    - Clippings used in School; also used for Judge Advocate General's School lectures
      - On Germany (Box 64)
        [64-23]
      - On North and East Europe (Box 65)
        [65-1]
      - On Central Europe (Box 65)
        [65-2]
      - On Progress of the War, 2 folders (Box 65)
        [65-3; 65-4]
  - Later German Activities and Interests
    - "Findings, Conclusions, Recommendations, and Analyses concerning the United States Civil Affairs/Military Government Organization" prepared by Daniel Cos Fahey, Jr. (Box 65)
      [65-5]
    - Papers concerning an Arbeitstagung der Institut zur Förderung Öffentlicher Angelegenheiten, on the topic: "Über das Problem der Neugliederung der Länder in der Bundersrepublik" July 20, 1950 (Box 65)
      [65-6]
    - Re expellees from East Europe, 2 folders (Box 65)
      [65-7; 65-8]
    - Re denazification, 2 folders (Box 65)
      [65-9; 65-10]
    - Re cartels in Germany (Box 65)
      [65-11]
    - Bonn Constitution
      - Stenographic reports of meetings 1-12 of the Parliamentarischer Rat 1948-1949 (Box 65)
        [65-12]
      - Proposal for new German Constitution by Friedrich Glum 1948 (Box 65)
        [65-13]
      - Minutes of meeting of Military Governors and Minister-Presidents of the Western Zones 1948 (Box 65)
        [65-14]
      - Draft of basic laws November 11, 1948-December 10, 1948 (Box 65)
        [65-15]
      - Further proposals 1948-1949 (Box 65)
        [65-16]
      - Historic German Constitution (Box 66)
        [66-1]
    - Southwest German State, 3 folders (Box 66)
      [66-2; 66-4; 66-5]
    - Southwest German State (re proposed Baden-Württemburg Constitution (Box 66)
      [66-3]
    - Baden-Württemburg (Box 66)
      [66-6]
    - Baden-Württemburg-Draft of a law for Verwaltungs Gerichtsbarkeit 1954 (Box 66)
      [66-7]
    - German State Constitutions (Hamburg, Bremen, Niedersachsen, Nordrhein-Westfalen, Gross-Hessen) (Box 66)
      [66-8]
    - German State Constitutions (Rhein-Palatinate, Nordrhein-Westfalen, Württemberg-Hohnzollern, Baden, Saar) (Box 66)
      [66-9]
    - German State Constitutions (Hessen) (Box 66)
      [66-10]
    - Soviet Zone of Germany, 4 folders (Box 66)
      [66-11; 66-13; 66-14; 66-15]
    - Soviet Zone of Germany-Constitutional Development (Box 66)
      [66-12]
    - Berlin
      - General, 4 folders (Box 67)
        [67-1; 67-2; 67-3; 67-7]
      - General (include "A Survey of Greater Berlin" by Homer Thomas and James K. Pollock) 1944 (Box 67)
        [67-4]
      - "Special Report: Berlin Industrial and Unemployment Survey" prepared by OMG, Berlin Sector Intelligence, Report 31 1949 (Box 67)
        [67-5]
      - "Economic Trends in Western Berlin" prepared by HICOG, Division of Economic Affairs, Reports 4-5 1950 (Box 67)
        [67-6]
    - Parliament (Bundestag)
      - Bundesanzeiger 1953, 1956 (Box 67)
        [67-8]
      - Drafts of laws on sexual equality 1953-1954 and military, 1956 and election law, 1956 (Box 67)
        [67-9]
      - Lists of Bundestag members 1953-1957 (Box 67)
        [67-10]
      - Record of voting in Bundestag 1953-1957 (Box 67)
        [67-11]
      - Draft laws and protocols from the 2nd election period 1953-1957 (Box 67)
        [67-12]
      - Draft laws and protocols from the 1st and 2nd election period 1949-1957 (Box 67)
        [67-13]
    - Conference: "Military Occupations and Political Change April 1967 (Box 67)
      (include papers by Freidrich, Merkl, and Holborn)
      [67-14]
    - Conference: "Military Occupations and Political Change April 1967 (Box 67)
      (include paper by Krieger)
      [67-15]
    - Military Government of Germany by H. Philip Mettger; include James K. Pollock criticisms, 1954 (Box 67)
      [67-16]
    - Manuscript of Pollock-Thomas study, "Germany in power and eclipse" 1952, 15 folders (Box 68)
      [68-1 to 68-15]
    - University of Michigan survey of German provinces 1944-1945
      - Correspondence (Box 68)
        [68-16a]
      - Maps, 2 folders (Box 68)
        [68-16b; 68-17]
      - Rheinprovinz (Box 68)
        [68-18]
      - Hanover (Box 68)
        [68-19]
      - Westfalen and Lippe (Box 68)
        [68-20]
      - Beden (Box 68)
        [68-21]
      - Thüringen (Box 68)
        [68-22]
      - Sachsen and Hamburg (Box 68)
        [68-23]
      - Sachsen (Box 68)
        [68-24]
      - Anhalt and Braunschwig (Box 68)
        [68-25]
      - Berlin (Box 69)
        [69-1]
      - Pommern (Box 69)
        [69-2]
      - Schlesien (Box 69)
        [69-3]
      - Bayern (annex) (Box 69)
        [69-4]
  - German Election Studies
    - Shelf list of materials 1956, 1965 (Box 69)
      [69-6]
    - Bundestag Elections
      - Official statistics and other data 1949, 1953 (Box 69)
        [69-7]
      - Official statistics 1957 (Box 69)
        [69-8]
      - Official statistics 1961 (Box 69)
        [69-9]
      - Official statistics and "Wahlbewerber," 1965 (Box 69)
        [69-10]
    - German Electoral Law of 1956
      - Pollock Research Outlines (Box 69)
        [69-11a]
      - History of German Electoral Experience (Box 69)
        [69-11b]
      - Study by John M. Gaines (Box 69)
        [69-11c]
      - Legislative History (Box 69)
        [69-12]
      - Aspects of Voting Behavior (Box 69)
        [69-13]
      - Aspects of Voting Behavior (Box 69)
        [69-14]
      - Analysis of Operation (Box 69)
        [69-15]
      - Studies of 1957 election results, 2 folders (Box 69)
        [69-16; 69-17]
      - Memoranda on results of the study by Peter Sperlich (Box 69)
        [69-18]
    - Various studies and papers
      - German reapportionment 1963 (Box 70)
        [70-1]
      - Transcript of interviews concerning Bundestag election 1961 (Box 70)
        [70-2]
      - Methodology and approach for observing 1965 Bundestag elections (Box 70)
        [70-3]
      - Field reports on 1954 German parliamentary elections (Box 70)
        [70-4]
      - Paper: "Barometric Constituencies in Germany and the 1965 elections" (Box 70)
        [70-5]
      - Paper: "Barometer Areas in Western Germany" 1964 (Box 70)
        [70-6]
      - Graphic and statistical material on German electoral districts, 3 folders (Box 70)
        [70-7; 70-8; 70-9]
      - West German elections (student papers) (Box 70)
        [70-19]
      - German elections and election law papers (Box 70)
        [70-20]
      - Paper: "The Political Role of Women in the German Federal Republic" 1952 (Box 70)
        [70-21]
      - Paper: "Political Parties and Public Opinion Research in Western Germany, 1947-1955" 1955 (Box 70)
        [70-22]
      - Paper pertaining to the incomes of employees of the German Ministry of Justice, "Vertraulich" 1952 (Box 70)
        [70-23]
    - Bundestag Elections
      - 1953
        - General (Box 70)
          [70-11]
        - Statistical data, 6 folders (Box 70)
          [70-12 to 70-17]
        - James K. Pollock Paper: "The West German Electoral Law of 1953" (preliminary draft) (Box 70)
          [70-18]
  - Franz Lieber Foundation
    - Correspondence
      - Unfiled 1959-1960 (Box 71)
        [71-1]
      - A 1954-1955 (Box 71)
        [71-2]
      - Ankeny, Dewalt 1951-1957 (Box 71)
        [71-3]
      - B 1951-1956 (Box 71)
        [71-4]
      - C 1952-1958 (Box 71)
        [71-5]
      - Connell, Lawrence C. 1952-1954 (Box 71)
        [71-6]
      - D 1954-1955 (Box 71)
        [71-7a]
      - Directors file 1951-1957 (Box 71)
        [71-7b]
      - Expense account (current) 1956-1960 (Box 71)
        [71-8a]
      - Expense accounts, old 1954-1955 (Box 71)
        [71-8b]
      - F 1952-1957 (Box 71)
        [71-9a]
      - Foundation miscellaneous (Box 71)
        [71-9b]
      - G 1951-1958 (Box 71)
        [71-10a]
      - Hamm, William, Jr. (Box 71)
        [71-10b]
      - H 1952-1958 (Box 71)
        [71-11]
      - Harrison, Gilbert A. 1951-1952 (Box 71)
        [71-12]
      - I 1956-1959 (Box 71)
        [71-13]
      - J 1954 (Box 71)
        [71-14a]
      - K 1951-1959 (Box 71)
        [71-14b]
      - L 1951-1958 (Box 71)
        [71-14c]
      - Littell, Franklin H. 1953-1955 (Box 71)
        [71-17]
      - Littell, Franklin H. 1956-1959 (Box 71)
        [71-16]
      - Littell, Franklin H. 1957-1958 (Box 71)
        [71-15]
      - M 1951-1959 (Box 71)
        [71-18]
      - Mahler, Ernst 1951-1957 (Box 71)
        [71-19]
      - Merthon, Lawrence 1956-1959 (Box 71)
        [71-20]
      - Newsletters 1957-1959 (Box 71)
        [71-21]
      - O 1952-1956 (Box 71)
        [71-22]
      - P 1953-1957 (Box 71)
        [71-23a]
      - R 1952-1956 (Box 71)
        [71-23b]
      - Reports
        - James K. Pollock personal reports 1951-1956 (Box 71)
          [71-24]
        - Periodic Reports from Germany on Foundation activities September 1953-January 1959 (Box 71)
          [71-25]
        - Periodic Reports from Germany on Foundation activities April 1951-July 1958 (Box 71)
          [71-26]
        - Special Reports, 2 folders (Box 71)
          [71-27; 71-28]
      - S 1953-1959 (Box 72)
      - U 1959 (Box 72)
      - Uihlein, Joseph E. 1952-1958 (Box 72)
      - V 1952-1956 (Box 72)
      - W 1952-1956 (Box 72)
      - Weyerhäuser, Frederick K. 1952-1957 (Box 72)
- European Election Studies 1920s-1957, 1.5 linear feet
  European Election Studies (1.5 linear ft.; 1920s-1957) is a series of research data and other materials from Pollock's study of different French and English elections. Most of the results of these studies were published in professional journals. Pollock's German election files have been maintained in the Germany series. This series includes extensive data on French elections from the 1920s to the 1950s with special emphasis on the 1930s, and British elections from 1918 to the late 1960s including complete data on parliamentary elections from 1918 to 1935 and 1945 to 1950, and special reports on party strength, campaign literature, proportional representation and electoral districts.
  - France
    - Chamber of Deputies. Data sheets for elections of 1928, 1932, 1936, 2 folders (Box 72)
    - Legislative election 1956 (Box 72)
    - Election propaganda 1920s-1930s (Box 72)
    - Election propaganda 1928 including L'Echo de Paris, La Francaise (Box 72)
    - Miscellanea 1926-1928 (Box 72)
    - Miscellanea 1934 (Box 72)
    - Paper: "A Study of Bye Elections in France" by Max P. Heavenrich, Jr. 1934 (Box 72)
    - Paper: "An Areal Approach to Voting in France" by Robert E. Powers 1937 (Box 72)
  - Britain
    - 1964 election
      - Report by James K. Pollock, S. Elderveld, and L. Laing on the 1964 British election trip (Box 72)
      - Documents concerning postal voting (Box 72)
      - Documents concerning nominations, etc (Box 72)
      - Documents supplied to presiding officer at a polling station (Box 72)
      - Documents including instructions, etc. to staff employed at election (Box 72)
      - Documents re Conservative and Unionist Party (Box 72)
    - Various elections
      - 1950s (Box 72)
      - List of Parliamentary Constituencies. 1955 (Box 72)
      - Election data and codes 1950s (Box 72)
      - Constituencies 1950, 1957 (Box 72)
      - Code sheets 1955 (Box 72)
      - Analytical data 1950, 2 folders (Box 72)
      - Paper: "British Election Studies, 1950" 1950, 2 folders (Box 72)
      - Miscellanea 1950 (Box 72)
      - Miscellanea 1951 (Box 72)
      - Data sheets on British Parliamentary Constituencies 1918-1935, 6 folders (Box 73)
      - Data sheets on British Parliamentary Constituencies 1945-1950, 6 folders (Box 73)
      - Material on party strength in Great Britain, 2 folders (Box 73)
      - "British by-Elections Between the Wars" (Box 73)
      - British election pamphlets 1929, 2 folders (Box 73)
      - Labor and Conservative Party election pamphlets 1931 (Box 73)
      - Lists of electors 1926-1927 (Box 73)
      - Political parties study 1929 (Box 73)
- University of Michigan 1924-1967, 3.7 linear foot
  University of Michigan is divided into subseries. The first relates to administrative matters within the department of political science and to Pollock's other activities at the University. This subseries covers the period of 1931 to 1967 and measures 0.2 linear feet. Most of Pollock's University of Michigan activities are best documented in the different chronological correspondence files. The second and largest is comprised of Course Materials (3.7 lin. ft.; 1924-1967) is further arranged by course number and by topic. The papers arranged by course number (2.2 linear feet) are in ascending order and include many handwritten notes for course lectures, bibliographies, reading lists and schedules, exams and weekly questions, some student papers, published papers by Pollock and others, and documents used in class. Papers arranged by topic (1.5 linear feet) relate to many facets of political science, both national and international. Most extensive is the set of papers related to German government, and of particular interest are the records related to the trip Pollock took to Germany with other professors and academics in 1934, and the field survey he conducted with students on the 1953 Budestag elections in Germany.
  - Committee/departmental materials
    - Reports on Faculty Services 1948 and Economic Status of the Faculty, 1945 (Box 74)
    - Reports on Economic Status of the Faculty 1944-1945 (Box 74)
    - Political Science Department Miscellaneous 1963-1967 (Box 74)
    - Statistics and records of the introductory courses 1931-1932 (Box 74)
    - Extension Service class: "Problem of State Government" 1937 (Box 74)
  - Political Science Course Materials
    - Arranged by Course Number
      - 1-- American Government
        - Class notes circa 1930-1950 (Box 74)
        - Exam questions and outlines 1924-1934, 2 folders (Box 74)
        - Weekly questions 1929-1932 (Box 74)
      - 2 -- State Government
        - Exam questions and outlines 1924-1941, 2 folders (Box 74)
        - Lectures 1950s (Box 74)
        - Notes Undated, 3 folders (Box 74)
        - Weekly questions 1929-1932 (Box 74)
      - 52 -- Comparative European Governments (see also P.S. 140, 350 and 741)
        - Lecture, class notes, exams and outlines 1946-1955, 1965-1967, 3 folders (Box 74)
      - 68 -- Foreign Affairs: Exam and class notes 1939 (Box 74)
      - 113 -- Political Parties
        - Election Costs in Michigan circa 1936 (Box 74)
        - Exams 1940-1944 (Box 74)
        - Exams and outlines 1940-1943 (Box 74)
        - Notes Undated, 2 folders (Box 74)
        - Notes circa 1930s (Box 75)
        - Notes circa 1940s (Box 75)
        - Reading Period Plan 1935 (Box 75)
      - 113 and 114
        - Work groups, ca. 1938-1939, 2 folders (Box 75)
        - Statistics 1938-1943 (Box 75)
      - 114 -- Comparative Electoral Systems, pre-1945, 2 folders (Box 75)
      - 116 -- Propaganda and Public Opinion
        - Lecture notes, n.d (Box 75)
        - Outlines and Exams 1940-1943 (Box 75)
        - 116s (summer) 1943 (Box 75)
      - 130 -- National Administration
        - Outlines and exams 1926-1929 (Box 75)